Hello friends, welcome to your YouTube
channel. This is going to be
very important,
so please watch the video till the end.
Friends, we will meet again today with a new vacancy.
Today, your vacancy has come out from
ICICI Bank.
Your recruitment has come out on various posts.
Today, in this video, I will
tell you from when to when your forms will be filled, what is the
application fee, what
qualification has been
asked of you in it, so for complete information, do
watch the video till the end. If you have
not liked the video yet, then
like and share it. If you are on the channel for the first
time, then definitely subscribe to the channel. So
let's start the video. If we
talk about the total number of posts, then your vacancies have come out for
approximately 2650 posts. Postman,
that is, for which posts have your vacancies
come out, so here your recruitment has come out for PO Clerk, Relationship
Manager and other posts.
When is the online date for Jagiyani to apply?  By when will they be filled?
Your forms have
started being made from 15th December 2022 and
your forms will be filled till 3rd February 2023.
What is your application fee in this? Your
application fee is for General,
OBC, Use SSC and S10 Pick i.e. those who
are Divyang candidates. Here almost
no fee has been kept for any candidate. The
forms of all the candidates will be filled absolutely free.
Talking about the further limit, your
minimum age should be 18 years.
What should be your qualification in this?
If you have done 10th, 12th and
graduation, then you will be eligible for this vacancy.
Selection
process i.e. how will you be selected in this, then
your selection is that first you will have an
interview and you will be
selected through documentation. So for this, that
is, what is going to be your salary?
Your minimum salary is from 24000 to
maximum
62000 per month. You will get salary i.e. every
month  Your mount is going to be very good
and your job location is
All of India, that is, you belong to any state of India,
any status or any blood,
you are going to be eligible for this vacancy
and if we talk about experience, then anyone
can apply, those who have experience can also
apply,
this is going to be online, how did you like the information,
do tell us in the comment section,
like and share the video, if you come to the channel for the
first time then definitely subscribe to the channel,
Jai Hind, Jai Bharat.